我吃掉一整罐橄榄的话 你会给我多少钱
Hey, how much you give me to eat this whole jar of olives?
我一毛都不会给你 但你欠我2块9毛5
I won't give you anything, but you'll owe me 2.95.
成交
Done.
我需要地图
Hi. I need an atlas. I need an atlas.
为什么 你要交报告吗
Why? Do you have a report due?
我跟我认识的外交官有约会
I have a date with this diplomat I met...
我在联合国外面做免费按摩时认识他
...while I was giving free massages outside the U.N.
我不知道他的国家在哪里
And I don't know where his country is.
先从在联合国外面做免费按摩说起吧
Okay, let's start with the free massages at the U.N.
那是我的新活动 我想身体舒服的话就能缔造和平
Oh, it's my new thing. I figure, bodies at peace make peace.
你可以拿到第一座诺贝尔按摩奖
Wow. You might just get the first Nobel Prize in rubbing.
这家伙来自哪个国家
So, what country is this guy from?
他的国名里有个G
There's a G in there.
- 到底是哪里   - 看地图就知道了
- Where's that?     - In your atlas.
我没有地图
I don't have an atlas.
等一下 我有地球仪
Oh, but wait, I do have a globe. Hold on.
菲比 这家伙是什么样的人
So, Pheebs, what's this guy like?
他非常…
Well, he's very...
亮眼 你知道吗
...dashing, you know?
非常优雅 他不会说英文
And, um, very, very sophisticated. And he doesn't speak English...
但根据他的翻译所说的 他非常喜欢我
...but according to his translator, he totally gets me.
好吧 拿去
Okay, here you go.
这是什么
What is this?
地球仪
It's a globe.
也是削铅笔机
And a pencil sharpener.
谁要影印 我要去影印店
Hey, anybody need anything copied? I'm going to the Xerox place.
不用了 谢谢
Uh, no, thanks.
好吧 听着 给我一些可以影印的东西
Okay, listen, just give me anything I can make two of.
如果你没东西要影印 为什么你要去影印店
If you don't have anything to copy, why are you going there?
你要去那里泡那个辣妹吗
Yeah, are you just going down there to gawk at that hot girl...
肚脐眼穿洞的辣妹
...with the bellybutton ring again?
对 你要一起来吗
Yeah. You wanna come?
当然要
Yeah.
# 没有人告诉你活着有多累 #
# So no one told you life was gonna be this way #
# 上班受罪 口袋空空 爱情变累赘 #
# Your job's a joke, you're broke, your love life's D.O.A. #
# 寂寞又潦倒 受气又受累 #
# It's like you're always stuck in second gear #
# 日复一日 年复一年 #
# When it hasn't been your day, #
# 时运不济 活着受罪 #
# your week, your month, or even your year #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# but I'll be there for you #
# 纵有狂风暴雨 #
# When the rain starts to pour #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# I'll be there for you #
# 支持一如往昔 #
# Like I've been there before #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# I'll be there for you #
# 你我相偎相依 #
# 'Cause you're there for me too #
快点 可洛 先处理好顾客
Come on, Chloe. Finish up with your customer first.
快点 可洛…
Come on, Chloe. Come on, Chloe.
需要我效劳吗
Can I help you?
你知道吗
Uh, you know what?
我们在考虑要不要影印
We're having second thoughts about our, uh, copying needs.
我们需要多一点时间考虑
And, uh, we'll need a little more time to think about it.
可洛 我们来换位置 暗恋你的人来了
Chloe, switch with me. There are some guys here who got a crush on you.
好吧 他是在讽刺我们
Okay, that hurt us.
两位 自从今天早上后 我一直没见到你们
Hi, guys. I haven't seen you since this morning.
这个嘛…
Well, uh...
你知道的
You know.
明晚你们要做什么
Hey, what are you guys doing tomorrow night?
我们两个吗
Both of us?
或许吧 那吓到你们了吗
Maybe. Does that scare you?
别紧张 艾萨克要到费城俱乐部当DJ
Relax. It's just Isaac's deejaying at The Philly.
- 你们该来看看的   - 我们一定到
- You should come.     - Oh. We'll be there.
太棒了 到时候见
Great. I'll, uh, see you then.
好的 摇吧
All right. Rock on.
他说跟你一起散步 让这个陌生城市有家的感觉
He says that walking with you makes this strange city feel like home.
我也是 虽然这个城市就是我的家
Aw. Me too. Although this city is my home.
我是在说蠢话 别跟他翻译我说的话
So that's dumb, what I said. Don't tell him I said that.
随便编一些事情给他听
Um, just... You make something up.
太棒了 谢谢
Nice. Thank you.
到了 这是我家
This is me. Here.
你的眼睛非常漂亮
Your eyes are very pretty.
谢谢
Thank you very much.
Oh, thank you.
他想吻你
He would like to kiss you.
好吧 你知道吗 现在你不必那么做
Okay. You know what? You don't have to do that now.
不 不是他 不 是你才对
No, no, not him. No, you don't.
好吧 气氛都破坏了
Okay. Well, the moment's over.
看吧 就在那里
See, there it is right there.
哇 真的好小
Wow, it's small.
对 但赛吉说德国人花了六星期
Yeah, but Sergei said it took the Germans six weeks...
才跨越他的国家
...to get all the way across it.
你很开心 对吧
So you had fun, huh?
对 除了…你知道的 在约会时
Yeah. Except for, you know, when you're on a date...
我们处得非常好
...and you're getting along really great...
但翻译一直在打断我们
...but the guy's translator keeps getting in the way?
我不知道
No.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
瑞秋在房里吗
What, is, uh, Rach in her room?
她还在上班 但她要我请你打电话给她
Oh. No, she's still at work, but she told me to tell you to call her.
什么她要取消跟我的约会 她怎么能那么做
Oh, what? Is she gonna cancel on me again? How could she do this?
她不知道今天是我们的周年纪念日吗
Doesn't she know it's our anniversary?
好吧 罗斯 我对这件事的了解仅止于此
All right, uh, Ross, this is the extent of my knowledge on the subject.
"打电话给瑞秋"
"Call Rachel."
下面写了什么
What's that on the bottom?
我的涂鸦 一只戴着礼帽的瓢虫
Oh. That's my doodle of a ladybug with a top hat. Ha, ha.
他真的蛮漂亮的
She's fancy.
- 喂   - 甜心
- Hello?     - Hey, honey.
- 喔 嗨   - 发生了什么事
- Oh, hi.     - Hey. What's going on?
货运出了问题 我得处理这笔订单
Well, there was a disaster in shipping and I've gotta get this order in.
甜心 真的很抱歉 看起来我得加班一整晚
Honey, I'm so sorry, but it looks like I'm gonna be here all night.
什么何不让我过去呢
What? Well, um, how about I come up there?
不 甜心 拜托 我有很多事要处理
No, no, no, honey, please. I just have too much to deal with.
总之今晚我要跟赛吉约会
Anyway, I'm going out with Sergei again tonight, and, um...
你能过来跟翻译约会吗
Could you come and be the translator's date?
在我们的独处时间 你们两个可以溜掉
So that when we... You know, it's time for our alone time, you two can split off?
他有点可爱
You know, he's kind of cute.
你是说他真的很可爱
"Kind of cute" like, "really kind of cute"?
或跟你的朋友"走后门哈利"一样可爱
Or "kind of cute" like your friend Spackle-Back Larry?
别那样叫他
Hey, don't call him that.
他叫做"走后门哈利"
His name is Spackle-Back Harry.
（中央咖啡厅）
你知道吗 或许我们该出发了
Hey, you know what? Maybe we should get going.
可洛要我们几点到
I mean, what time did Chloe say to get there?
- 十点半   - 现在几点
- Uh, 10:30.     - What time is it now?
四点半
Four-thirty.
- 好吧 我们再待一会   - 对
- Yeah, all right. So we'll hang out.     - Yeah.
还记得她提过我们能三人行的事吗
Hey, remember when she brought up that thing about the three of us?
对 我记得可清楚了
Yes, vividly.
- 她是在开玩笑的吧   - 我想应该是的
- She was kidding about that, right?     - Yeah, I think so.
我想应该是的
Yeah, I think so.
天啊 如果今晚真的发生那种事 还蛮奇怪的
God, it'd be weird if that situation presented itself tonight, huh?
没错 我是说…
Yeah. Yeah, I mean, uh...
我们该怎么做呢
...what would we do?
兄弟 我不知道
Ha, ha. Dude, I don't know. Ha-ha-ha.
- 她是开玩笑的   - 对
- She was kidding.     - Yeah.
她是…
She was...
为了以防万一 我们该制订规则
Just in case, we should come up with a set of ground rules.
对 没错
Yeah. For sure.
好吧 第一条规则应该是
Okay. You probably want the first one to be:
千万别张开眼睛
"Never open your eyes."
你知道吗 因为你不会希望在做的时候
You know? Because you don't want to be doing something...
抬头往上看吧
...and then look up, right?
看到你不想看的事
And see something that you don't want to be seeing.
对 好点子 太棒了
Yeah. Good call. Nice.
等一下…
Hold it. Hold it.
如果我闭上眼睛
What if my eyes are closed, and...
我的手在那里
And my hand is out there...
好吧 一定要张开眼睛
Aah! Okay, eyes open at all times.
喔 嘿
Oh, hey.
我们如何决定我们该…
How do we decide where we, ahem...
各自应该在…
...you know, each would, ahem, you know...
- 哪个位置   - 对
- ...be?     - Right. Right.
我们可以丢铜板决定
Well, you know, we could flip for it.
我想是吧 但正面跟反面怎么分
I guess. But, like, what's heads and what's tails?
如果你连那个都不知道 我不想跟你一起做这件事
Well, if you don't know that, then I don't want to do this with you.
不 我正看着订单
No, no, no. I am looking at a purchase order right here...
上面写得很清楚 我们订了蔚蓝海岸比基尼
...and it clearly states that we ordered the Riviera bikini...
不同的尺寸跟颜色
...in a variety of sizes and colors and...
这跟我穿什么有关系吗
What does it matter what I'm wearing?
我能跟你的上司谈一谈吗 谢谢 我愿意等
Could I please speak to your supervisor? Thank you. We're holding.
嗨
Hi.
天啊 你来这里做什么
My God. What are you doing here?
你说你无法离开 所以…
Well, you said you couldn't go out, so...
你带了野餐过来 超棒的男朋友
You brought a picnic. Ugh. What a boyfriend.
够了 星期一我要开始化妆
That's it. On Monday, I start wearing makeup.
罗斯 这真的太棒了 但我得处理危机
Ross, honey, this is very nice, but I've got a crisis.
对 但我准备了北非小米
Yeah, but I've got couscous.
甜心 抱歉 我知道今天是我们的周年纪念日
Honey. Honey, I'm sorry. I know it's our anniversary...
我在电话里说过我没时间停下来
...but I told you on the phone I don't have time to stop.
好吧 你不必停下来 我是隐形人 就当我不在这里
Okay, you don't have to stop. I'm invisible. I'm not here.
对 可是我…
Yeah, but I don't...
谁批准那笔订单的
Who approved that order?
但我没有同事叫做马克•罗宾森
Well, there is no Mark Robinson in this office.
- 帮我打电话给马克   - 我爱马克 你认识马克吗
- Get me Mark on the phone.     - Ugh. I love Mark. Do you know Mark?
- 当然   - 我得查一下手边的资料
- Yeah.     - Let me check that with what I've got here.
好吧 038不是本店代码 038是亚特兰大的代码
All right, see, 038 is not the number for this store. Zero-three-eight is Atlanta.
要胡椒吗
Heh. Pepper?
- 我不要   - 好吧 抱歉
- None for me.     - Okay, sorry. Whoo.
抱歉 我说过分店代码错了
I'm sorry. As I was saying, the store number is wrong.
对不起 可是…天啊
And I'm sorry, but... Oh, my God!
好了 没事了
Okay. It's fine.
太棒了
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
对不起 我再回你电话
Excuse me, I'm sorry, I'm gonna have to call you back.
我的办公室来了一个疯子
I've got Shemp in my office.
- 你在做什么   - 对不起
- What are you doing?     - I'm sorry.
有人挂掉电话了
But, um, hey, oh, somebody's off the phone.
要不要在火边来杯酒 我可以再生一次火
How about a glass of wine by the fire? I can get it going again...
罗斯 你没在听 我没时间停下来
Ross, you're not listening. I don't have time to stop.
- 少来了 你连十分钟都没有   - 我没有十分钟
- Come on, you don't have 10 minutes?     - I don't have 10 minutes.
- 苏菲 她没有十分钟吗   - 罗斯 我说过我没有时间
- Sophie, does she have 10 minutes?     - Hey, Ross. I told you, I don't.
别对我大叫 好吗 这是整个星期我们见面最久的一次
Don't yell at me, okay? This is the most I've seen you all week.
听着 现在我没空跟你说 我得在时限内完成工作
Look, I cannot do this right now, okay? I've got a deadline.
你能回家吗 我们晚点再谈
Would you just go home? I'll talk to you later.
- 对 等一下   - 再见
- Yeah, but wait...     - Goodbye.
那是我们的打洞机
Uh, actually, that's our three-hole punch.
- 嘿   - 嗨
- Hey.     - Hi.
听着 之前发生的事
Look, um, about what happened earlier...
我完全了解 你压力很大
Whoa. I completely understand. You were stressed.
我会给你机会跟我道歉
I was gonna give you a chance to apologize to me.
为什么 因为我让你在你的办公室对我发脾气
For what? For letting you throw me out of your office?
你无权跑到我的办公室 罗斯
You had no right coming down to my office, Ross.
你不能带着野餐篮跑到别人的办公室
You do not bring a picnic basket to somebody's work...
除非他们是公园巡警
...unless maybe they were a park ranger.
对 请原谅我想跟女朋友一起庆祝我们的周年纪念日
Yeah, well, excuse me for wanting to be with my girlfriend on our anniversary.
天啊 我真是个大混蛋
Boy, what an ass am I.
但是我说过我没时间
But I told you I didn't have the time.
对 你总是没时间
Yeah, well, you never have the time.
我是说我觉得我不像有女朋友了 瑞秋
I mean, I don't feel like I have a girlfriend anymore.
罗斯 你要我怎么做
Ross, what do you want from me?
你要我辞掉工作 让你觉得你有女朋友
You want me to quit my job so you can feel like you have a girlfriend?
不 或许那是个好点子 你得了解那只是一份工作
No. But it would nice if you'd realize that it's just a job.
只是一份工作
Just a job?
对
Yes.
罗斯 你知道这是我一生中第一次我在做我在乎的事吗
Ross, do you realize this is the first time in my life I'm doing something I care about?
这是我一生中第一次在做我拿手的事吗
This is the first time in my life I'm doing something I'm actually good at?
如果你无法了解
I mean, if you don't get that...
我了解 好吗 我了解 也为你感到开心
No, hey, I get that. Okay? I get that and I'm happy for you.
但我厌倦了跟你的答录机谈恋爱
I'm tired of having a relationship with your answering machine.
- 我不想再那么做了   - 我也是
- I don't know what to do anymore.     - Well, neither do I.
这跟马克有关吗
Is this about Mark?
- 天啊   - 好吧 跟他无关
- Oh, my God.     - Okay, it's not.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
我无法老是跟你吵这件事 罗斯
I cannot keep having this same fight over and over again, Ross.
不 你让我不知道该怎么办
No, you're making this too hard.
我让你不知道该怎么办 好 你要我怎么做
I'm making this too hard? What do you want me to do?
我不知道
I don't know. I don't know.
听着 或许我们该休息一下
Look, ugh, maybe we should just take a break.
好吧 你说的对
Okay, okay. Fine. You're right.
我们休息一下 让自己冷静下来
Let's, uh... Let's take a break. Let's cool off, okay?
我们去吃冷冻优格吧
Let's get some frozen yogurt or something.
不是
No.
我们该分手了
A break from us.
过去五年来 装订有了很大的进步
And the advances in collating in the past five years.
我们刚刚买了一部X5000
I mean, we just got in an X-5000, you know?
X5000让X50看起来像T71
The X-5000 makes an X-50 look like a T-71.
恐龙先生来了
Hey, it's the dinosaur guy.
- 嗨 罗斯   - 可洛
- Hi, Ross.     - Oh, hi, Chloe.
我跟你介绍一下我的朋友
I want you to meet some friends of mine.
这家伙是我的英雄 他会拿着资料过来
This guy's my hero. He comes in with some stuff...
要我们放大四倍
...he wants it blown up 400 percent.
我们说我们办不到 他说你们非得这么做不可
We say we don't do that. He says, "You gotta."
你们知道吗 我们办到了
And you know what? We did it.
现在有人要放大资料四倍 我们都会说我们得学罗斯精神
And now any time anybody wants 400, we just say, "Let's Ross it."
那是唯一合理的地方
And that's the only color that comes in.
可洛 你有铜板借我投保险套贩卖机吗
Yo, Chloe. Do you have a quarter for the condom machine?
你来这里做什么
So, what are you doing here?
我以为今晚你们要去吃晚餐庆祝周年纪念日
I thought tonight was your big anniversary dinner.
对 计划有变
Yeah, a little change of plans.
我们决定分手
Uh, we're gonna break up instead.
我会说一点法文
Oh, and I can also speak a little French.
为什么我说了什么
Why? What did I say?
你问我今晚要不要跟你上床
Well, you just asked if I wanted to go to bed with you tonight.
天啊
Oh, my God.
难怪我在墨利斯咖啡厅得到超棒的服务
No wonder I get such great service at Cafe Maurice.
等一下
Knock, knock, knock.
你能告诉赛吉我很喜欢
Hi. Um, could you please tell Sergei that, um, I was fascinated...
布特罗斯•盖里在"纽约时报"发表的言论吗
...by what Boutros Boutros-Ghali said in the New York Times?
你没提到布特罗斯•盖里
You didn't say, "Boutros Boutros-Ghali."
布特罗斯•盖里
Boutros Boutros-Ghali.
他说他也是
He says he was too.
真有趣
Interesting.
我还蛮好奇的
Uh, so I was wondering...
在你们又聊起来之前
Before you get all talky again...
你能告诉赛吉
...um, could you also please tell Sergei...
我很喜欢他的西装吗
...that I really like his suit.
他说谢谢 今晚你也很漂亮
Uh, he said, "Thank you very much. You look very pretty tonight.
你的头发跟阳光一样闪亮 你是厨师吗
Your hair, golden like the sun." So you're a chef?
我考虑自己开家餐厅
I'm also thinking of opening up my own restaurant.
- 真的吗   - 摩妮卡
- Oh, really?     - Monica...
我们能在菜单后面谈一谈吗
...could I talk to you behind my menu, please?
- 你在做什么   - 我在聊天
- What are you doing?     - Well, I was having a conversation.
但米夏对你非常有兴趣
Yeah, but Mischa's so interested in you...
赛吉跟我却没办法说话
...that Sergei and I haven't been able to say two words to each other.
你要我呆呆地坐在这里听你们三个聊天
What do you want me to do? Sit here while the three of you have a conversation?
那就真的太棒了 谢谢
That would be great. Thank you.
- 喂   - 嗨 我是马克
- Hello?     - Oh, hi. It's Mark.
什么 我有口臭吗
What? Is it my breath?
不 抱歉 我以为你是别人 嗨…
No. Sorry. I just thought you were somebody else. Hi.
嗨 听着 我正要留话给你
Hi, well, look, I was just gonna leave a message.
今晚不是你的周年纪念日晚餐吗
Isn't tonight your anniversary dinner?
瑞秋 你没事吧
Rach? Are you okay?
对 我很好
Yeah, I'm fine.
你要聊一聊吗 我可以过去
You wanna talk? I mean, I can come over.
不 真的  拜托 没事的
No, really, no. Please. That's okay.
我立刻过去 我会带中国菜过去
All right. I'm coming over and I'm bringing Chinese food.
- 我不饿   - 是我要吃的
- Oh, yeah, I'm not hungry.     - It's for me.
好的 再见
Okay. Bye.
- 你打算怎么办   - 我能做什么
- So, what'll you do?     - What can I do?
对方要分手 你只能接受
One person wants to break up, you break up.
不行 你们不一样 打电话跟她谈一谈
Hey, no way. Come on, this is you guys. Call her and work it out.
少来了 我们刚刚大吵一架 我不能等一下再打吗
Come on. We just had this huge fight. Don't I have to wait a while?
这又不是吃完饭后不能游泳 快去打电话
Hey, this isn't like swimming after you eat. Pick up your phone.
吃完东西后不能游泳是个迷
You know that whole swimming thing is a myth.
对 跟我的蓝尼叔叔说吧
Yeah, tell that to my Uncle Lenny.
为什么 他怎么了
Why? What happened to him?
没事 他只是相信那套说法
Nothing. He just really believes in that.
然后我们愚蠢地大吵一架 这真的很可怕
Ugh. And then we got into this big, stupid fight... It was awful.
我跟他说他把我当成公园巡警
I told him he treats me like a park ranger, something, ugh...
后来…
And then...
我跟他说我要分手
...I told him I wanted to take a break.
我不想分手
I don't want to take a break.
我很遗憾
Well, I'm sorry.
- 春卷   - 不要
- Egg roll?     - No.
然后我打电话给他 他不在
And then I called him, and he wasn't there.
或许他只是出去了
He's probably just out.
谢谢 那真的帮了我一个大忙 我很高兴你来了
Oh, thank you. That's very helpful. I'm glad you came over.
- 喂   - 嗨 是我
- Hello?     - Hi, it's me.
- 我好高兴你打电话来   - 真的吗
- Hi. Oh, I'm so glad you called.     - Really?
我一直在想这真的很疯狂 你不觉得我们能解决这个问题吗
I've been thinking this is crazy. Don't you think we can work on this?
你要喝什么
Hey, what do you want to drink?
是谁在说话
Who's that?
没有啊
Nobody?
我可以喝完苹果汁吗
Is it okay if I finish the apple juice?
是 马克吗
Is that Mark?
- 甜心 听着 他刚好过来   - 对 我明白了
- Ooh, honey, look, he just came over...     - Yeah, got it.
恐龙先生 看看你 你一副苦瓜脸的模样
Hey, Dinosaur Guy. Look at you, so sad.
- 来跳舞吧   - 我不要 谢谢
- Come dance.     - Uh, that's okay. Thanks.
嘿
Hey.
你不必笑 你只要跳舞
You don't have to smile. You just have to dance.
听着 我不想跳舞 我想喝一杯 好吗
Look, I don't feel like dancing. I feel like having a drink, okay?
好吧 两杯啤酒
Oh, okay. Hey, two beers.
兽医说时间到了
And the vet said it was time.
在地球的另一端
And so from half-a-world away...
我妈妈将话筒放在他的耳边
...while my mother held the phone to his ear...
我跟我的狗道别
...I said goodbye to my dog...
使用七种语言
...in seven languages.
- 能给我面纸吗   - 没问题
- Could I have a tissue?     - Oh, yeah, sure.
希望你不会意外地把它塞进鼻孔里
I just hope you don't accidentally suck it up through your nose...
害自己窒息死掉
...and choke on it.
赛吉要为我今晚的行为道歉
Ugh. Sergei would like to apologize for my behavior tonight.
跟他说我接受他的致歉
Well, tell him, "Apology accepted."
他太不可思议了 三年来第一次有人要跟我说话
He's unbelievable. For the first time in three years, someone wants to talk to me.
你觉得他会让我享受一下吗 不
But do you think he would let me enjoy that? No.
你这个笨外交官 为什么他不学英文 赛吉
You silly diplomat. Why don't you learn some English, Sergei?
对不起 他不是帮你付晚餐钱吗
Excuse me, but, um, ahem, isn't he paying for your dinner?
他的狗才死不久
Hey, the man's dog just died.
我刚刚辞职了
I have just resigned my post.
你能陪我到彩虹室吗
Would you care to accompany me to the Rainbow Room?
我有外交官折价券
I have diplomatic coupons.
这是我的荣幸
It would be my pleasure.
我的男伴有折价券
My guy has coupons.
你的男伴连折价券都不会说
Your guy can't even say "coupons."
盘子
Uh, plate.
- 盘子 对   - 盘子
- Plate. Yes. Plate. Plate.     - Plate. Plate.
盘子
Plate.
看吧 我们不需要他们
See, we don't need them.
盘子
Plate?
对
Yeah.
# 造化弄人 命运交缠 #
# Sleight of hand And twist of fate #
# 因为她 我辗转难眠 #
# On a bed of nails She makes me wait #
我喜欢这首歌
I like this song.
你已经开始跳舞了
Well, you're practically dancing already.
- 你何不过来这边跳舞   - 不
- Why don't you just do it over here?     - Oh, no.
怎么你结婚了吗
What are you, married?
我不在乎
Because that's okay.
你一定要在家
Oh, be home, be home, be home...
Be home, be home, be home.
你不在家
You're not home.
# 你若即若离 #
# With or without you #
还是笑不出来
Still no smile?
# 你放弃了自己 #
# And you give yourself away #
# 你放弃了 #
# And you give #
# 你放弃了自己 #
# And you give yourself away #
美国人
American.
- 美国人   - 美国人
- American.     - American.
美国人 这是非常难的语官
American. You know, it's a very hard language.
我们再来一次
Let's do it again.